<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE BlastOutput PUBLIC "-//NCBI//NCBI BlastOutput/EN" "http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/dtd/NCBI_BlastOutput.dtd">
<BlastOutput>
  <BlastOutput_program>blastp</BlastOutput_program>
  <BlastOutput_version>BLASTP 2.8.1+</BlastOutput_version>
  <BlastOutput_reference>Stephen F. Altschul, Thomas L. Madden, Alejandro A. Sch&amp;auml;ffer, Jinghui Zhang, Zheng Zhang, Webb Miller, and David J. Lipman (1997), &quot;Gapped BLAST and PSI-BLAST: a new generation of protein database search programs&quot;, Nucleic Acids Res. 25:3389-3402.</BlastOutput_reference>
  <BlastOutput_db>nr</BlastOutput_db>
  <BlastOutput_query-ID>Query_235289</BlastOutput_query-ID>
  <BlastOutput_query-def>d1hx6a1241</BlastOutput_query-def>
  <BlastOutput_query-len>241</BlastOutput_query-len>
  <BlastOutput_param>
    <Parameters>
      <Parameters_matrix>BLOSUM62</Parameters_matrix>
      <Parameters_expect>10</Parameters_expect>
      <Parameters_gap-open>11</Parameters_gap-open>
      <Parameters_gap-extend>1</Parameters_gap-extend>
      <Parameters_filter>F</Parameters_filter>
    </Parameters>
  </BlastOutput_param>
<BlastOutput_iterations>
<Iteration>
  <Iteration_iter-num>1</Iteration_iter-num>
  <Iteration_query-ID>Query_235289</Iteration_query-ID>
  <Iteration_query-def>d1hx6a1241</Iteration_query-def>
  <Iteration_query-len>241</Iteration_query-len>
<Iteration_hits>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>1</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gi|9626361|ref|NP_040692.1|</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>major capsid protein [Salmonella virus PRD1] &gt;gi|116654|sp|P22535.2|CAPSD_BPPRD RecName: Full=Major capsid protein P3; AltName: Full=Protein P3 &gt;gi|56966724|pdb|1W8X|A Chain A, Structural Analysis Of Prd1 &gt;gi|56966725|pdb|1W8X|B Chain B, Structural Analysis Of Prd1 &gt;gi|56966726|pdb|1W8X|C Chain C, Structural Analysis Of Prd1 &gt;gi|56966727|pdb|1W8X|D Chain D, Structural Analysis Of Prd1 &gt;gi|56966728|pdb|1W8X|E Chain E, Structural Analysis Of Prd1 &gt;gi|56966729|pdb|1W8X|F Chain F, Structural Analysis Of Prd1 &gt;gi|56966730|pdb|1W8X|G Chain G, Structural Analysis Of Prd1 &gt;gi|56966731|pdb|1W8X|H Chain H, Structural Analysis Of Prd1 &gt;gi|56966732|pdb|1W8X|I Chain I, Structural Analysis Of Prd1 &gt;gi|56966733|pdb|1W8X|J Chain J, Structural Analysis Of Prd1 &gt;gi|56966734|pdb|1W8X|K Chain K, Structural Analysis Of Prd1 &gt;gi|56966735|pdb|1W8X|L Chain L, Structural Analysis Of Prd1 &gt;gi|215744|gb|AAA32445.1| major capsid protein [Salmonella virus PRD1] &gt;gi|61394116|gb|AAX45916.1| major capsid protein [Salmonella virus PRD1]</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>NP_040692</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>395</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>432.18</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>1110</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>1.08417e-149</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>1</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>241</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>15</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>244</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>228</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>229</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>11</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>241</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>LRNQQAMAANLLQQARQIVLQQSYPVIQQVETTQTFDPANRRSVFDVTPANVGIVKGFLVKVTAAITNNNHATEAVALTDFGPANLVQQRVVIYYDPDNNQRHTETSGWHLHFVNTAKQGAPFLSSMMVTDSPIKYGDVMNVIDAPATIAAGATGELTMYYWVPLAYSETDLTGAVLANVPQSKQRLKLEFANNNTAFAAVGANPLEAIYQGAGAADCEFEEEISSYTVYQSYLDQLPVGQ</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>LRNQQAMAANL--QARQIVLQQSYPVIQQVET-QTFDPANR-SVFDVTPANVGIVKGFLVKVTAAITNN-HATEAVALTDFGPANLVQR--VIYYDPDN-QRHTETSGWHLHFVNTAKQGAPFLSSM-VTDSPIKYGDVMNVIDAPATIAAGATGELTMYYWVPLAYSETDLTGAVLANVPQSKQRLKLEFANNNTAFAAVGANPLEAIYQGAGAADCEFEE--ISYTVYQSYLDQLPVGQ</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>LRNQQAMAANL  QARQIVLQQSYPVIQQVET QTFDPANR SVFDVTPANVGIVKGFLVKVTAAITNN HATEAVALTDFGPANLVQ+  VIYYDPDN QRHTETSGWHLHFVNTAKQGAPFLSSM VTDSPIKYGDVMNVIDAPATIAAGATGELTMYYWVPLAYSETDLTGAVLANVPQSKQRLKLEFANNNTAFAAVGANPLEAIYQGAGAADCEFEE   SYTVYQSYLDQLPVGQ</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>2</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gi|6137459|pdb|1CJD|A</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>Chain A, The Bacteriophage Prd1 Coat Protein, P3, Is Structurally Similar To Human Adenovirus Hexon &gt;gi|6137460|pdb|1CJD|B Chain B, The Bacteriophage Prd1 Coat Protein, P3, Is Structurally Similar To Human Adenovirus Hexon &gt;gi|6137461|pdb|1CJD|C Chain C, The Bacteriophage Prd1 Coat Protein, P3, Is Structurally Similar To Human Adenovirus Hexon &gt;gi|13096435|pdb|1HX6|A Chain A, P3, The Major Coat Protein Of The Lipid-Containing Bacteriophage Prd1. &gt;gi|13096436|pdb|1HX6|B Chain B, P3, The Major Coat Protein Of The Lipid-Containing Bacteriophage Prd1. &gt;gi|13096437|pdb|1HX6|C Chain C, P3, The Major Coat Protein Of The Lipid-Containing Bacteriophage Prd1. &gt;gi|17943134|pdb|1HB9|A Chain A, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 wild type virion, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|17943135|pdb|1HB9|B Chain B, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 wild type virion, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|17943136|pdb|1HB9|C Chain C, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 wild type virion, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|17943137|pdb|1HB9|D Chain D, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 wild type virion, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|17943138|pdb|1HB9|E Chain E, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 wild type virion, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|17943139|pdb|1HB9|F Chain F, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 wild type virion, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|17943140|pdb|1HB9|G Chain G, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 wild type virion, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|17943141|pdb|1HB9|H Chain H, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 wild type virion, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|17943142|pdb|1HB9|I Chain I, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 wild type virion, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|17943143|pdb|1HB9|J Chain J, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 wild type virion, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|17943144|pdb|1HB9|K Chain K, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 wild type virion, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|17943145|pdb|1HB9|L Chain L, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 wild type virion, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|17943158|pdb|1HB5|A Chain A, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 P3-shell, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|17943159|pdb|1HB5|B Chain B, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 P3-shell, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|17943160|pdb|1HB5|C Chain C, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 P3-shell, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|17943161|pdb|1HB5|D Chain D, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 P3-shell, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|17943162|pdb|1HB5|E Chain E, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 P3-shell, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|17943163|pdb|1HB5|F Chain F, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 P3-shell, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|17943164|pdb|1HB5|G Chain G, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 P3-shell, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|17943165|pdb|1HB5|H Chain H, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 P3-shell, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|17943166|pdb|1HB5|I Chain I, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 P3-shell, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|20149968|pdb|1GW7|A Chain A, Quasi-atomic Resolution Model Of Bacteriophage Prd1 Capsid, Obtained By Combined Cryo-em And X-ray Crystallography. &gt;gi|20149969|pdb|1GW7|B Chain B, Quasi-atomic Resolution Model Of Bacteriophage Prd1 Capsid, Obtained By Combined Cryo-em And X-ray Crystallography. &gt;gi|20149970|pdb|1GW7|C Chain C, Quasi-atomic Resolution Model Of Bacteriophage Prd1 Capsid, Obtained By Combined Cryo-em And X-ray Crystallography. &gt;gi|20149971|pdb|1GW7|D Chain D, Quasi-atomic Resolution Model Of Bacteriophage Prd1 Capsid, Obtained By Combined Cryo-em And X-ray Crystallography. &gt;gi|20149972|pdb|1GW7|E Chain E, Quasi-atomic Resolution Model Of Bacteriophage Prd1 Capsid, Obtained By Combined Cryo-em And X-ray Crystallography. &gt;gi|20149973|pdb|1GW7|F Chain F, Quasi-atomic Resolution Model Of Bacteriophage Prd1 Capsid, Obtained By Combined Cryo-em And X-ray Crystallography. &gt;gi|20149974|pdb|1GW7|G Chain G, Quasi-atomic Resolution Model Of Bacteriophage Prd1 Capsid, Obtained By Combined Cryo-em And X-ray Crystallography. &gt;gi|20149975|pdb|1GW7|H Chain H, Quasi-atomic Resolution Model Of Bacteriophage Prd1 Capsid, Obtained By Combined Cryo-em And X-ray Crystallography. &gt;gi|20149976|pdb|1GW7|I Chain I, Quasi-atomic Resolution Model Of Bacteriophage Prd1 Capsid, Obtained By Combined Cryo-em And X-ray Crystallography. &gt;gi|20149977|pdb|1GW7|J Chain J, Quasi-atomic Resolution Model Of Bacteriophage Prd1 Capsid, Obtained By Combined Cryo-em And X-ray Crystallography. &gt;gi|20149978|pdb|1GW7|K Chain K, Quasi-atomic Resolution Model Of Bacteriophage Prd1 Capsid, Obtained By Combined Cryo-em And X-ray Crystallography. &gt;gi|20149979|pdb|1GW7|L Chain L, Quasi-atomic Resolution Model Of Bacteriophage Prd1 Capsid, Obtained By Combined Cryo-em And X-ray Crystallography. &gt;gi|334878464|pdb|1GW8|A Chain A, Quasi-atomic Resolution Model Of Bacteriophage Prd1 Sus607 Mutant, Obtained By Combined Cryo-em And X-ray Crystallography. &gt;gi|334878465|pdb|1GW8|B Chain B, Quasi-atomic Resolution Model Of Bacteriophage Prd1 Sus607 Mutant, Obtained By Combined Cryo-em And X-ray Crystallography. &gt;gi|334878466|pdb|1GW8|C Chain C, Quasi-atomic Resolution Model Of Bacteriophage Prd1 Sus607 Mutant, Obtained By Combined Cryo-em And X-ray Crystallography. &gt;gi|334878467|pdb|1GW8|D Chain D, Quasi-atomic Resolution Model Of Bacteriophage Prd1 Sus607 Mutant, Obtained By Combined Cryo-em And X-ray Crystallography. &gt;gi|334878468|pdb|1GW8|E Chain E, Quasi-atomic Resolution Model Of Bacteriophage Prd1 Sus607 Mutant, Obtained By Combined Cryo-em And X-ray Crystallography. &gt;gi|334878469|pdb|1GW8|F Chain F, Quasi-atomic Resolution Model Of Bacteriophage Prd1 Sus607 Mutant, Obtained By Combined Cryo-em And X-ray Crystallography. &gt;gi|334878470|pdb|1GW8|G Chain G, Quasi-atomic Resolution Model Of Bacteriophage Prd1 Sus607 Mutant, Obtained By Combined Cryo-em And X-ray Crystallography. &gt;gi|334878471|pdb|1GW8|H Chain H, Quasi-atomic Resolution Model Of Bacteriophage Prd1 Sus607 Mutant, Obtained By Combined Cryo-em And X-ray Crystallography. &gt;gi|334878472|pdb|1GW8|I Chain I, Quasi-atomic Resolution Model Of Bacteriophage Prd1 Sus607 Mutant, Obtained By Combined Cryo-em And X-ray Crystallography. &gt;gi|334878473|pdb|1GW8|J Chain J, Quasi-atomic Resolution Model Of Bacteriophage Prd1 Sus607 Mutant, Obtained By Combined Cryo-em And X-ray Crystallography. &gt;gi|334878474|pdb|1GW8|K Chain K, Quasi-atomic Resolution Model Of Bacteriophage Prd1 Sus607 Mutant, Obtained By Combined Cryo-em And X-ray Crystallography. &gt;gi|334878475|pdb|1GW8|L Chain L, Quasi-atomic Resolution Model Of Bacteriophage Prd1 Sus607 Mutant, Obtained By Combined Cryo-em And X-ray Crystallography. &gt;gi|334878496|pdb|1HB7|A Chain A, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 sus1 mutant, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|334878497|pdb|1HB7|B Chain B, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 sus1 mutant, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|334878498|pdb|1HB7|C Chain C, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 sus1 mutant, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|334878499|pdb|1HB7|D Chain D, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 sus1 mutant, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|334878500|pdb|1HB7|E Chain E, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 sus1 mutant, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|334878501|pdb|1HB7|F Chain F, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 sus1 mutant, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|334878502|pdb|1HB7|G Chain G, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 sus1 mutant, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|334878503|pdb|1HB7|H Chain H, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 sus1 mutant, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|334878504|pdb|1HB7|I Chain I, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 sus1 mutant, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|334878505|pdb|1HB7|J Chain J, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 sus1 mutant, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|334878506|pdb|1HB7|K Chain K, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 sus1 mutant, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography. &gt;gi|334878507|pdb|1HB7|L Chain L, quasi-atomic resolution model of bacteriophage PRD1 sus1 mutant, obtained by combined cryo-EM and X-ray crystallography.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>1CJD_A</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>394</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>431.409</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>1108</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>1.69512e-149</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>1</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>241</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>14</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>243</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>228</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>229</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>11</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>241</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>LRNQQAMAANLLQQARQIVLQQSYPVIQQVETTQTFDPANRRSVFDVTPANVGIVKGFLVKVTAAITNNNHATEAVALTDFGPANLVQQRVVIYYDPDNNQRHTETSGWHLHFVNTAKQGAPFLSSMMVTDSPIKYGDVMNVIDAPATIAAGATGELTMYYWVPLAYSETDLTGAVLANVPQSKQRLKLEFANNNTAFAAVGANPLEAIYQGAGAADCEFEEEISSYTVYQSYLDQLPVGQ</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>LRNQQAMAANL--QARQIVLQQSYPVIQQVET-QTFDPANR-SVFDVTPANVGIVKGFLVKVTAAITNN-HATEAVALTDFGPANLVQR--VIYYDPDN-QRHTETSGWHLHFVNTAKQGAPFLSSM-VTDSPIKYGDVMNVIDAPATIAAGATGELTMYYWVPLAYSETDLTGAVLANVPQSKQRLKLEFANNNTAFAAVGANPLEAIYQGAGAADCEFEE--ISYTVYQSYLDQLPVGQ</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>LRNQQAMAANL  QARQIVLQQSYPVIQQVET QTFDPANR SVFDVTPANVGIVKGFLVKVTAAITNN HATEAVALTDFGPANLVQ+  VIYYDPDN QRHTETSGWHLHFVNTAKQGAPFLSSM VTDSPIKYGDVMNVIDAPATIAAGATGELTMYYWVPLAYSETDLTGAVLANVPQSKQRLKLEFANNNTAFAAVGANPLEAIYQGAGAADCEFEE   SYTVYQSYLDQLPVGQ</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>3</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gi|215732|gb|AAA32442.1|</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>major capsid protein [Enterobacteria phage PR4] &gt;gi|41323065|gb|AAR99754.1| major capsid protein [Enterobacteria phage PR772] &gt;gi|61393941|gb|AAX45545.1| major capsid protein [Enterobacteria phage L17] &gt;gi|61394009|gb|AAX45607.1| major capsid protein [Enterobacteria phage PR4] &gt;gi|61394079|gb|AAX45669.1| major capsid protein [Enterobacteria phage PR772]</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>AAA32442</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>395</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>430.254</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>1105</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>5.1822e-149</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>1</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>241</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>15</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>244</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>227</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>228</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>11</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>241</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>LRNQQAMAANLLQQARQIVLQQSYPVIQQVETTQTFDPANRRSVFDVTPANVGIVKGFLVKVTAAITNNNHATEAVALTDFGPANLVQQRVVIYYDPDNNQRHTETSGWHLHFVNTAKQGAPFLSSMMVTDSPIKYGDVMNVIDAPATIAAGATGELTMYYWVPLAYSETDLTGAVLANVPQSKQRLKLEFANNNTAFAAVGANPLEAIYQGAGAADCEFEEEISSYTVYQSYLDQLPVGQ</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>LRNQQAMAANL--QARQIVLQQSYPVIQQVET-QTFDPANR-SVFDVTPANVGIVKGFLVKVTAAI-KNNHATEAVALTDFGPANLVQR--VIYYDPDN-QRHTETSGWHLHFVNTAKQGAPFLSSM-VTDSPIKYGDVMNVIDAPATIAAGATGELTMYYWVPLAYSETDLTGAVLANVPQSKQRLKLEFANNNTAFAAVGANPLEAIYQGAGAADCEFEE--ISYTVYQSYLDQLPVGQ</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>LRNQQAMAANL  QARQIVLQQSYPVIQQVET QTFDPANR SVFDVTPANVGIVKGFLVKVTAAI  NNHATEAVALTDFGPANLVQ+  VIYYDPDN QRHTETSGWHLHFVNTAKQGAPFLSSM VTDSPIKYGDVMNVIDAPATIAAGATGELTMYYWVPLAYSETDLTGAVLANVPQSKQRLKLEFANNNTAFAAVGANPLEAIYQGAGAADCEFEE   SYTVYQSYLDQLPVGQ</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>4</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gi|61393974|gb|AAX45576.1|</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>major capsid protein [Enterobacteria phage PR3]</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>AAX45576</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>395</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>430.254</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>1105</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>6.2414e-149</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>1</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>241</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>15</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>244</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>227</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>228</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>11</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>241</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>LRNQQAMAANLLQQARQIVLQQSYPVIQQVETTQTFDPANRRSVFDVTPANVGIVKGFLVKVTAAITNNNHATEAVALTDFGPANLVQQRVVIYYDPDNNQRHTETSGWHLHFVNTAKQGAPFLSSMMVTDSPIKYGDVMNVIDAPATIAAGATGELTMYYWVPLAYSETDLTGAVLANVPQSKQRLKLEFANNNTAFAAVGANPLEAIYQGAGAADCEFEEEISSYTVYQSYLDQLPVGQ</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>LRNQQAMAANL--QARQIVLQQSYPVIQQVET-QTFDPANR-SVFDVTPANVGIVKGFLVKVTAAI-KNNHATEAVALTDFGPANLVQR--VIYYDPDN-QRHTETSGWHLHFVNTAKQGAPFLSSM-VTDSPIKYGDVMNVIDAPATIAAGATGELTMYYWVPLAYSETDLTGAVLANVPQSKQRLKLEFANNNTAFAAVGANPLEAIYQGAGAADCEFEE--ISYTVYQSYLDQLPVGQ</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>LRNQQAMAANL  QARQIVLQQSYPVIQQVET QTFDPANR SVFDVTPANVGIVKGFLVKVTAAI  NNHATEAVALTDFGPANLVQ+  VIYYDPDN QRHTETSGWHLHFVNTAKQGAPFLSSM VTDSPIKYGDVMNVIDAPATIAAGATGELTMYYWVPLAYSETDLTGAVLANVPQSKQRLKLEFANNNTAFAAVGANPLEAIYQGAGAADCEFEE   SYTVYQSYLDQLPVGQ</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>5</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gi|61394043|gb|AAX45638.1|</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>major capsid protein [Enterobacteria phage PR5]</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>AAX45638</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>395</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>429.098</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>1102</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>1.84345e-148</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>1</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>241</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>15</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>244</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>226</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>228</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>11</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>241</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>LRNQQAMAANLLQQARQIVLQQSYPVIQQVETTQTFDPANRRSVFDVTPANVGIVKGFLVKVTAAITNNNHATEAVALTDFGPANLVQQRVVIYYDPDNNQRHTETSGWHLHFVNTAKQGAPFLSSMMVTDSPIKYGDVMNVIDAPATIAAGATGELTMYYWVPLAYSETDLTGAVLANVPQSKQRLKLEFANNNTAFAAVGANPLEAIYQGAGAADCEFEEEISSYTVYQSYLDQLPVGQ</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>LRNQQAMAANL--QARQIVLQQSYPVIQQVET-QTFDPANR-SVFDVTPANVGIVKGFLVKVTAAI-KNNHATEAVALTDFGPANLVQR--VIYYDPDN-QRHTETSGWHLHFVNTAKQGAPFLSSM-VTDSPIKYGDVMNVIDAPATIAAGATGELTMYYWVPLAYSETDLTGAVLANVPQSKQRLKLEFANNNTAFAAVGANPLEAIYQGAGAADCKFEE--ISYTVYQSYLDQLPVGQ</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>LRNQQAMAANL  QARQIVLQQSYPVIQQVET QTFDPANR SVFDVTPANVGIVKGFLVKVTAAI  NNHATEAVALTDFGPANLVQ+  VIYYDPDN QRHTETSGWHLHFVNTAKQGAPFLSSM VTDSPIKYGDVMNVIDAPATIAAGATGELTMYYWVPLAYSETDLTGAVLANVPQSKQRLKLEFANNNTAFAAVGANPLEAIYQGAGAADC+FEE   SYTVYQSYLDQLPVGQ</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>6</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gi|13096620|pdb|1HQN|A</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>Chain A, The Selenomethionine Derivative Of P3, The Major Coat Protein Of The Lipid-Containing Bacteriophage Prd1. &gt;gi|13096621|pdb|1HQN|B Chain B, The Selenomethionine Derivative Of P3, The Major Coat Protein Of The Lipid-Containing Bacteriophage Prd1. &gt;gi|13096622|pdb|1HQN|C Chain C, The Selenomethionine Derivative Of P3, The Major Coat Protein Of The Lipid-Containing Bacteriophage Prd1.</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>1HQN_A</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>394</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>420.239</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>1079</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>4.8989e-145</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>1</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>241</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>14</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>243</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>224</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>225</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>11</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>241</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>LRNQQAMAANLLQQARQIVLQQSYPVIQQVETTQTFDPANRRSVFDVTPANVGIVKGFLVKVTAAITNNNHATEAVALTDFGPANLVQQRVVIYYDPDNNQRHTETSGWHLHFVNTAKQGAPFLSSMMVTDSPIKYGDVMNVIDAPATIAAGATGELTMYYWVPLAYSETDLTGAVLANVPQSKQRLKLEFANNNTAFAAVGANPLEAIYQGAGAADCEFEEEISSYTVYQSYLDQLPVGQ</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>LRNQQAXAANL--QARQIVLQQSYPVIQQVET-QTFDPANR-SVFDVTPANVGIVKGFLVKVTAAITNN-HATEAVALTDFGPANLVQR--VIYYDPDN-QRHTETSGWHLHFVNTAKQGAPFLSSX-VTDSPIKYGDVXNVIDAPATIAAGATGELTXYYWVPLAYSETDLTGAVLANVPQSKQRLKLEFANNNTAFAAVGANPLEAIYQGAGAADCEFEE--ISYTVYQSYLDQLPVGQ</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>LRNQQA AANL  QARQIVLQQSYPVIQQVET QTFDPANR SVFDVTPANVGIVKGFLVKVTAAITNN HATEAVALTDFGPANLVQ+  VIYYDPDN QRHTETSGWHLHFVNTAKQGAPFLSS  VTDSPIKYGDV NVIDAPATIAAGATGELT YYWVPLAYSETDLTGAVLANVPQSKQRLKLEFANNNTAFAAVGANPLEAIYQGAGAADCEFEE   SYTVYQSYLDQLPVGQ</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>7</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gi|1393335874|gb|PWT78035.1|</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>hypothetical protein C5B60_01770 [Chloroflexi bacterium]</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>PWT78035</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>399</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>89.3521</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>220</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>6.14309e-17</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>16</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>238</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>18</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>240</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>78</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>120</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>20</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>233</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>RQIVLQ-----QSY--PVIQQVETTQTFDPAN--RRSVFDVTPANVGIVKGFLVKVTAAITNNNHATEAVALTDFGPANLVQQRVVIYYDPDNNQRHTETSGWHLHFVNTAKQGAPFLSSMMVTDSPIKYGDVMN-VIDAPATIAAGATGELTMYYWVPLAYSETDLTGAVLANVPQSKQRLKLEFANNNTAFAAVGANPLEAIYQGAGAADCEFEEEISSYTVYQSYLDQLP</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>RQLILRGGALGQSYFPPAVDMWQQLNPILPASVGPGSVITIQLRNVGLVKRLVVELSAQV--NAGATSTQTLTALGLANLVSN--VTFIDLGNNTRINST-GWHLNAVSSVKRRRVF-AAAYASDTPNGYGNNNNRVMYAPTSIAANANTPIRFMLEIPFVKNNHDLRGAIFADVTNAVMQVQITL--NPQAFVSSTADPTLAVYQ-SGGADLASLSNV-AVQANQNYLDQLP</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>RQ++L+     QSY  P +   +      PA+    SV  +   NVG+VK  +V+++A +  N  AT    LT  G ANLV    V + D  NN R   T GWHL+ V++ K+   F ++   +D+P  YG+  N V+ AP +IAA A   +     +P   +  DL GA+ A+V  +  ++++    N  AF +  A+P  A+YQ +G AD      + +    Q+YLDQLP</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>8</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gi|1275230313|gb|ATS92580.1|</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>major capsid protein [Gluconobacter phage GC1]</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>ATS92580</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>399</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>63.5438</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>153</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>5.58884e-08</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>47</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>239</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>64</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>248</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>57</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>91</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>14</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>196</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>VTPANVGIVKGFLVKVTAAITNNNHATEAVALTDFGPANLVQQRVVIYYDPDNNQRHTETSGWHLHFVNTAKQGAPFLSSMMVTDSPIKYGDVMNV-IDAPATIAAGA--TGELTMYYWVPLAYSETDLTGAVLANVPQSKQRLKLEFANNNTAFAAVGANPLEAIYQGAGAADCEFEEEISSYTVYQSYLDQLPV</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>IQPRNVGLLRNILVRVEMEFVVPSGTTLTAG--EFGPAALLSG---VRFTDLNNLDRINTDGIHLALLASARNRQPAGAAFM-TDTPLGWGNNFGGGIAWPGASVSGTGQTVKVMMTYNVPIMYAEGDYRGAIYLGTTMANCNLNLTV--NPAFFAVSNSSAVDYGFKYDGTAPTVTSLKITS---YQDYLDQLPV</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>+ P NVG+++  LV+V       +  T      +FGPA L+     + +   NN     T G HL  + +A+   P  ++ M TD+P+ +G+     I  P    +G   T ++ M Y VP+ Y+E D  GA+      +   L L    N   FA   ++ ++  ++  G A      +I+S   YQ YLDQLPV</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>9</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gi|1431990210|gb|RCL78284.1|</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>GatB/YqeY domain-containing protein [PS1 clade bacterium]</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>RCL78284</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>150</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>41.5874</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>96</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>0.416155</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>23</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>82</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>57</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>122</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>24</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>35</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>6</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>66</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>SYPVIQQVETTQTFDPANRRSVFDVTPANVGIVKGFLVK------VTAAITNNNHATEAVALTDFG</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>SKMVKQRVESAETYKQANRQELVDQELEEIEIIKGFLPRQLDEDESRAAVENVINETEASGLKDMG</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>S  V Q+VE+ +T+  ANR+ + D     + I+KGFL +        AA+ N  + TEA  L D G</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>10</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gi|1431996398|gb|RCL84265.1|</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>GatB/YqeY domain-containing protein [PS1 clade bacterium]</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>RCL84265</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>150</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>39.2762</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>90</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>2.67209</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>23</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>82</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>57</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>122</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>23</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>34</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>6</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>66</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>SYPVIQQVETTQTFDPANRRSVFDVTPANVGIVKGFLVK------VTAAITNNNHATEAVALTDFG</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>SKMVKQRVESAETYKQANRQELVDQELEEIEIIKGFLPRQLDEDESRAAVESVIKETEASGLKDMG</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>S  V Q+VE+ +T+  ANR+ + D     + I+KGFL +        AA+ +    TEA  L D G</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>11</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gi|495793387|ref|WP_008517966.1|</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>GatB/YqeY domain-containing protein [alpha proteobacterium IMCC14465] &gt;gi|402511666|gb|EJW21927.1| hypothetical protein IMCC14465_03210 [alpha proteobacterium IMCC14465]</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>WP_008517966</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>150</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>39.2762</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>90</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>3.0256</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>23</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>82</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>57</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>122</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>22</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>34</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>6</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>66</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>SYPVIQQVETTQTFDPANRRSVFDVTPANVGIVKGFLVK------VTAAITNNNHATEAVALTDFG</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>SKMVKQRIESAETYKQANRQELVDQELEEIEIIKGFLPRQLDDDESRAAVESVIKETEASGLKDMG</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>S  V Q++E+ +T+  ANR+ + D     + I+KGFL +        AA+ +    TEA  L D G</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>12</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gi|1200433296|gb|OUV49743.1|</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>glutamyl-tRNA amidotransferase [Alphaproteobacteria bacterium TMED110]</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>OUV49743</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>150</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>38.891</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>89</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>3.29729</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>23</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>82</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>57</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>122</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>23</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>34</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>6</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>66</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>SYPVIQQVETTQTFDPANRRSVFDVTPANVGIVKGFLVK------VTAAITNNNHATEAVALTDFG</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>SKMVKQRVESAETYKQANRQELXDQELEEIEIIKGFLPRQLDEDESRAAVESVIKETEASGLKDMG</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>S  V Q+VE+ +T+  ANR+ + D     + I+KGFL +        AA+ +    TEA  L D G</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>13</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gi|519072307|ref|WP_020228182.1|</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>GNAT family N-acetyltransferase [Acidovorax sp. MR-S7] &gt;gi|524554268|dbj|GAD22149.1| predicted acyltransferase [Acidovorax sp. MR-S7]</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>WP_020228182</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>153</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>38.891</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>89</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>4.13274</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>94</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>152</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>36</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>90</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>21</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>31</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>8</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>61</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>YYDPDNNQRHTETSGWHLHFVNTAKQGAPFLSSMMVTDSPIKYGD--VMNVIDAPATIAAG</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>YQDPDDADRHA----WHL--LGRAEAGGPLLATLRVVDPGVKYTEPSIGRVVCAPEARGTG</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>Y DPD+  RH     WHL  +  A+ G P L+++ V D  +KY +  +  V+ AP     G</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
<Hit>
  <Hit_num>14</Hit_num>
  <Hit_id>gi|1181322576|ref|WP_084623461.1|</Hit_id>
  <Hit_def>DUF3108 domain-containing protein [Salinisphaera shabanensis]</Hit_def>
  <Hit_accession>WP_084623461</Hit_accession>
  <Hit_len>268</Hit_len>
  <Hit_hsps>
    <Hsp>
      <Hsp_num>1</Hsp_num>
      <Hsp_bit-score>39.6614</Hsp_bit-score>
      <Hsp_score>91</Hsp_score>
      <Hsp_evalue>4.36957</Hsp_evalue>
      <Hsp_query-from>102</Hsp_query-from>
      <Hsp_query-to>153</Hsp_query-to>
      <Hsp_hit-from>15</Hsp_hit-from>
      <Hsp_hit-to>66</Hsp_hit-to>
      <Hsp_query-frame>0</Hsp_query-frame>
      <Hsp_hit-frame>0</Hsp_hit-frame>
      <Hsp_identity>20</Hsp_identity>
      <Hsp_positive>25</Hsp_positive>
      <Hsp_gaps>0</Hsp_gaps>
      <Hsp_align-len>52</Hsp_align-len>
      <Hsp_qseq>RHTETSGWHLHFVNTAKQGAPFLSSMMVTDSPIKYGDVMNVIDAPATIAAGA</Hsp_qseq>
      <Hsp_hseq>RMTNTTGWRFHDRRCKRYGALCLLLVAMLDSPIAGADVMQTFDAQFKVKRGA</Hsp_hseq>
      <Hsp_midline>R T T+GW  H     + GA  L  + + DSPI   DVM   DA   +  GA</Hsp_midline>
    </Hsp>
  </Hit_hsps>
</Hit>
</Iteration_hits>
  <Iteration_stat>
    <Statistics>
      <Statistics_db-num>183393632</Statistics_db-num>
      <Statistics_db-len>66901926931</Statistics_db-len>
      <Statistics_hsp-len>0</Statistics_hsp-len>
      <Statistics_eff-space>0</Statistics_eff-space>
      <Statistics_kappa>0.041</Statistics_kappa>
      <Statistics_lambda>0.267</Statistics_lambda>
      <Statistics_entropy>0.14</Statistics_entropy>
    </Statistics>
  </Iteration_stat>
</Iteration>
</BlastOutput_iterations>
</BlastOutput>
